[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Victor, your money is ready!
- See you then.
He said he has a business
meeting at Jade Imperial.
We need to get in.
[METAL CLANKS]
[THUDS]
[METAL DOOR CREAKS]
Find a way to get in that bar.
We should split up.
- Have you seen Mr. Chan?
- He's in the VIP room.
Sir, are you alone?
None of your business.
Are you sure about the job
we took? I'm getting nervous.
Don't let anyone else in here.
We're almost there.
We have the item with us.
These people don't look
like a small-time syndicate.
I hope the pay is worth it.
It seems like our lives
are at stake here, Gabo.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Here they are.
- Victor!
- Mr. Chan.
(In Chinese) Happy New Year!
Take a seat.
[LUCAS] Mr. Chan.
We brought your order.
Easy, Lucas.
We aren't just here
to make a transaction.
We are here to celebrate.
[MR. CHAN] Good.
I like your gold.
Very in demand.
Big profit for me.
Next time, I order double
people, no problem.
Let's enjoy now.
Good. That's good to hear.
This is a good start
for our year.
Art, order the
most expensive liquor.
- Let's get drunk.
- No need.
[MR. CHAN] I will pay.
On me.
- [FINGER SNAPS]
- Yes, boss?
- Get the most expensive liquor.
- [WAITER] Yes, boss.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BOUNCER 1] Where are you going?
I'll just use the bathroom
[BOUNCER 2] You can't be here!
Scram!
Leave!
I thought the bathroom
was here.
[BOUNCER 2] Leave! Leave!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAITER] Excuse me, sir.
[GABO] Tekla.
Where are you going?
To the VIP area.
You already know what to do.
Go ahead. Be careful.
Go ahead.
Take care, okay?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
BOUNCER 1] Who is that for?
It's for the VIPs.
[BOUNCER 2] Okay. Come on.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hi.
Yes, sir?
Come sit with me.
Do you need something else?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FINGER SNAPS]
[MR. CHAN] Like what
we talked about.
200 million...
in cash.
[THUDDING]
Do I still have to count it?
No need.
You trust me,
I trust you.
Me, money, no problem.
I have lots of money.
Good thing we understand
each other.
Wait, why are you here?
You're still here?
Were you listening in
on our conversation?
Victor.
Don't worry about it.
[TEKLA] That's right.
I'm good at listening.
He told me to stay put
so, I'm just sitting here.
And you two?
Why are you still here?
Huh?
Get out.
Kick them out.
- Wait, wait!
- She's with us, boss.
Wait, me too?! [GROANS]
[GOON] Let's go, let's go!
- Come on, move.
- [TEKLA] Ouch!
- [IPE] Ow!
- [GOON] Get out!
- Get out!
- Boss, wait a second!
- Get out of here!
- Hey, be gentle with her!
- Ow! [SHRIEKS] Ack!
- Out!
- [THUDDING]
- [GROANING IN PAIN]
That hurt!
Gabo! [GROANS]
- [PANTING]
- What happened?
Looks like they caught on.
They kicked us out.
But Gabo,
we sniffed something out!
They have a huge transaction
going on inside!
Gabo, Mr. Chan
and Tiger's transaction...
is worth millions of pesos
and gold, right?!
Are we finally gonna make it?
Are we gonna make it big?!
We have a problem though.
There are tons of bodyguards!
And they're jacked too!
Looks like we're in a pinch,
Gabo.
We'll only die if we try
to catch them right now.
I'll take care of it.
I'll find a way
to capture Tiger.
[UWAK] Hopia!
- From Chinatown!
- [GROANS]
Hey.
We went to Chinatown.
Gabo is nowhere to be found.
I'm certain
that with how crowded it is,
you just didn't notice him.
With how crowded it is,
he wouldn't be able
to find Tiger or even catch him.
You two are always
doubting Gabo.
Can't you put
a little faith in him?
You know, Tomas,
with how long we've been
watching Gabo,
I'm a hundred percent sure
that he's gonna fail.
Can't you believe in him?
Let's bet on it!
Let's have a bet!
He'll capture Tiger!
- For how much?
- Alright!
- I'm down!
- Name your price.
- 5,000 pesos!
- [LAUGHTER]
And here I thought
you believe in him!
5,000 pesos?
- Here. 20,000 pesos.
- Alright! Twenty!
- Here.
- Deal!
- Best friend.
- Call!
Wait, wait, wait.
Who'll handle the money?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- It's Pops!
- Pops!
I don't know about you
but for me, I'm certain
that Gabo will succeed.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I really like the quality
of your gold.
Next week we will deliver
more gold.
I will look forward to that.
- (In Chinese) Thank you.
- [CLAPS]
They're coming.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- Let's move.
- Yeah.
Keep it on the low.
- [SAM] Excuse me.
- Hey!
[THUDDING] Ow!
- [TEKLA GROANS]
- I'm so sorry!
- [GABO] Watch it!
- Miss.
- You?!
- You again?!
What do you mean, "again"?!
[SAM] Are you stalking me?!
[GABO] And why would I do that?!
Maybe it's you
who's stalking me!
[SAM] Have some shame!
- Don't forget. You violated me!
- Hey!
It was you who violated me!
Didn't you kiss me?!
Scumbag!
- What now, huh?
- Sa-- Sam!
Want me to kiss you again, huh?
I'll really do it.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Gabo!
- [BONG] Gabo!
- [THUDDING]
[GABO GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Scoundrel! Do you know him?
Th-- that's the bastard
who stole a kiss from me!
That bastard!
- Hey! Enough!
- Seb!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Get up!
- Gabo, fight back!
You bastard...
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GABO GRUNTING]
- [KAREN] Sir! Stop!
- Seb, that's enough!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[THUDDING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- Seb!
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [BONG] Gabo!
- [KICK LANDS]
[TEKLA] Gabo, fight back!
Seb, stop it!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [TEKLA] Gabo!
[GABO SHOUTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [SEBASTIAN GRUNTING]
- Get him, Gabo!
- Hell yeah!
- That's it!
- Seb!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[GUN COCKS]
[SCREAMS] A gun!
You bastard!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- He's got a gun!
Want me to blow your head
into smithereens?
Do you know
that I'm an NCIA agent?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SEBASTIAN] You idiot!
Want me to blow your brains out?
Don't you that I'm NCIA? Huh?!
[KAREN] You just blew our cover.
This is the NCIA!
Victor Zafra, hands in the air!
[GUNSHOTS]
- Gabo!
Fall back!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS]
Gabo!
- Gabo!
- [BINOY] Gabo!
[GUNSHOTS]
[ARTURO] You have
to get out, Victor!
[GUNSHOTS]
[SEBASTIAN] Come on!
Let's follow them!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICTOR] Hurry!
Let's split, quick!
Move!
Faster! Open it, open it,
open it. Faster!
Go. Let's go.
Let's go, drive, drive, drive!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Here!
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[SAM] Move!
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SEBASTIAN] Come on,
let's follow him!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TEKLA] Gabo!
- I have to follow them!
- No! Gabo, don't!
- [TOLITS] Gabo, don't!
- [BINOY] Gabo!
- Gabo, stop!
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[VAN ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TEKLA] We have to help Gabo!
No! Didn't you see their guns?!
We don't have anything!
What is this, a suicide mission?
- Let him die if he wants to!
- What's with you?!
They're right, Tekla.
We're completely defenseless!
[TEKLA] I hope nothing bad
happens to Gabo.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FACE SHIELD THUDS]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
Someone's following us.
Gun them down!
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Victor!
- Lucas, we have to split up!
[VICTOR] I'll mislead them!
I need backup. Tell them
to go to Twin Phoenix, quick!
[CAR ENGINE REVS]
Victor's splitting.
- Go faster!
- [ARTURO] Alright!
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
Go to Twin Phoenix. Now!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[EARPHONE CLICKS]
- Team.
- Sam?
I'll follow Tiger.
Follow his men!
Copy.
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVS]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINES REVVING]
- Don't let them catch you!
- Can't you see that I won't?!
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [MOTOR ENGINE REVVING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARING]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ROARS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING,
ENGINE ROARS]
[SAM]
Castor, track Tiger down.
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [DIGITAL TRILLING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
They're gone.
Good job.
[SEBASTIAN]
Where are they?!
Dang it!
They slipped right through us!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [MOTOR ENGINE REVVING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DIGITAL TRILLING]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Ma'am Sam,
Tiger's at Twin Phoenix.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ROARS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[HEADLIGHTS CLICKING ON]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE STOPS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[NECK CRACKS]
[NUNCHUCKS SWISHING]
[CHAINS CLINKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND RUSTLING]
[WEAPONS CLINKING]
[JOINTS POPPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND RUSTLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC SWELLS]
If it lands heads...
I'll wipe every last one
of these bastards out.
But if it lands tails...
that means...
[COIN PINGING]
I'm never coming home alive.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
- [NUNCHUCKS SWISHING]
[METAL RODS CLACKING]
[WEAPONS SWISHING]
- [THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [WINDSHIELD SHATTERING]
[KICK LANDS]
[METAL ROD CLANGING]
[BLOWS LAND]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [WINDSHIELD SHATTERS]
- [FIREWORKS WHISTLING]
- [KICK LANDS]
[METAL RODS CLACKING]
[NUNCHUCKS SWISHING]
[THWACKING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [KICK LANDS]
[WINDSHIELD SHATTERS]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
[THWACKING]
[METAL ROD THUDDING]
[BODY THUDS]
[KICK LANDS]
[RHYTHMIC CLANGING
AND THUDDING]
- [WINDSHIELD SHATTERS]
- [NUNCHUCKS SWISHING]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [BODY SLAMMING ONTO CAR]
[RHYTHMIC CLANGING
AND THUDDING]
- [METAL RODS CLACKING]
- [KICK LANDS]
[RHYTHMIC CLANGING
AND THUDDING]
[THWACKING]
[BODY THUDS]
- [THRILLING MUSIC SWELLS]
- [NUNCHUCKS SWISHING]
[AXE SWISHING]
- [THWACKING]
- [BODIES THUDDING]
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HEAVY THUD]
[NECK CRACKS]
[MUSIC BECOMES OMINOUS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SEBASTIAN]
Sam! Sam!
They escaped!
We lost them!
Forget about them. It's more
important to catch Tiger.
Meet me at Twin Phoenix.
I'm going in.
Copy!
Turn around. Now!
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
- [METAL ROD CLANGS]
- Ah!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BLADE WHOOSHES]
[WEAPONS CLANGING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [SCREAMING, GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Who are you?!
What do you want from me?!
A huge bounty's been placed
on your head
for ruining the lives
of countless people.
You deserve to rot
behind bars!
You're making
a big mistake!
You don't know
who you're messing with!
[CAR ENGINE ROARS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Aah!
[WEAPONS CLANGING]
- Hey! [GRUNTS]
- [GUN CLATTERS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[ECHOING THWACK]
- [FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
- [WEAPONS CLANGING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WEAPON CLANGS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[WEAPONS CLANGING]
Aah!
[GOONS GRUNTING]
[KICK LANDS]
[THWACKS]
- [THWACKS]
- [GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THWACKS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
- Aah!
- [THWACKS]
Tiger!
Hey! Tiger!
Don't jump!
If you jump from there,
you'll fall to your death!
You're going to paint
the ground with your blood!
Hey! Stubborn, are you?
[GLASS BREAKS]
Ack!
[GOONS SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GOONS GROANING]
You think you can escape?!
[GRUNTS]
[VICTOR GRUNTS]
- Urgh!
- Stop!
[GUNSHOTS]
[VICTOR, MUFFLED]
Let go of me!
You can't catch me!
Aah!
[HOSE CREAKS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
You psycho!
You can't escape!
[SEBASTIAN] Team, apprehend
the suspects! Move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jacinto!
- Argh!
- [HOSE CREAKS]
Aah! Aah!
[HOSE WHIRRING]
[VICTOR GROANING]
[SAM] Stop!
[GUNSHOTS]
Victor Zafra,
you're under arrest.
- [SAM] Cuff him.
- [SEBASTIAN] Get up!
[HANDCUFFS RATTLING]
Walk.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
There goes our money.
You're going to be
an action star!
I have a job for you.
Let's just kill him off.
Easy.
What is this woman doing here?!
Do you know
what Gabo did to us?!
It's so humiliating!
Do we have to
grovel and beg
in order to survive?
- [SNIFFLES]
- [FLATLINES]
- Pa!
- I need your help.
My father is in the hospital.
I need money.
There are plenty
of missions I can give you.
Bring me Mr. Chan's gold bars.
It doesn't matter
if he's dead or alive.
- [THWACKS]
- Ah!
I saw the news about your son.
Yes, your daughter
arrested him.
I didn't do anything to you.
This can ruin our
good relationship, Ricardo.
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Just tell us who that guy is.
I had a buyer for that bike!
We could've used that money
for your father's operation!
If the patient doesn't
get immediate surgery,
he might not make it.
We're racing against time here.
Gabo! Help!
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Where can I find Mr. Chan?
We're making our move tonight.
I need to find that guy
who meddled with our operation.
We'll silence Mr. Chan.
- The Zafras are attacking!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
Boss!
- Ugh!
- [THWACKS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- Who are you?!
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- Let's get out of here!